<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TextView</string>
    <string name="random_text">


"The greatest glory in living lies not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall." -Nelson Mandela \n\n
"The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing." -Walt Disney \n\n
"Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life. Don't be trapped by dogma – which is living with the results of other people's thinking." -Steve Jobs \n\n
"If life were predictable it would cease to be life, and be without flavor." -Eleanor Roosevelt\n\n
"If you look at what you have in life, you'll always have more. If you look at what you don't have in life, you'll never have enough." -Oprah Winfrey\n\n
"If you set your goals ridiculously high and it's a failure, you will fail above everyone else's success." -James Cameron\n\n
"Life is what happens when you're busy making other plans." -John Lennon\n\n\n\n

        "Success is not final; failure is not fatal: It is the courage to continue that counts." -Winston S. Churchill\n\n
"Success usually comes to those who are too busy to be looking for it." -Henry David Thoreau\n\n
"The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing." -Walt Disney\n\n
"If you really look closely, most overnight successes took a long time." -Steve Jobs\n\n
"The secret of success is to do the common thing uncommonly well." -John D. Rockefeller Jr.\n\n
"I find that the harder I work, the more luck I seem to have." -Thomas Jefferson\n\n
"The real test is not whether you avoid this failure, because you won't. It's whether you let it harden or shame you into inaction, or whether you learn from it; whether you choose to persevere." -Barack Obama\n\n\n\n
\n
        Thanks ;)\n

        Sahil..\n
        (Email) - sahilkumar1bt@gmail.com \n\n
<!--        <a href ="https://instagram.com/its_s.a.h.i.l_?igshid=1hsjtgxbkyj2i">INSTAGRAM</a>-->
<!--        \n\n\n\n\n-->
        (Insta) - https://instagram.com/its_s.a.h.i.l_?igshid=1hsjtgxbkyj2i \n\n\n\n

    </string>


</resources>